When do we get to
the cheese? Soon.
This can't be right.
It's so small.
I had no idea when I ordered
this that it was actual size.
Come on. come on.
Hurry up. Let's go!
It's about time for
the official lighting
of the Christmas
extravaganza. Brad! Randy!
They're not here.
Where'd they go?
They're still out collecting money
for the school Christmas drive.
Oh. I can't wait. They can see it
later. Come on. come on. come on.
Honey. I hope you
didn't get back into
this whole competition thing
with Doc Johnson this year.
Please. I'm past it. OK?
I've nothing to prove.
This year I'm going
for a low-key approach.
All right. when I flick the switch.
it's gonna be kind of bright.
so you're gonna need
these sunglasses. Oh. Tim.
Don't look directly
at the snowman.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Mom? Dad?
Where'd you go?
We're still here.
Well. what do you think? Can
we put the kids in the middle?
Hi. Hey.
Hey. guys.
Pretty awesome
lights out there. huh?
It's really hot out there.
I don't know if all that
straw around the baby Jesus
is such a great idea.
Randy. he's the son of God.
He'll be fine.
Dad. everyone in the
whole neighborhood
is standing outside
of our house.
and they don't look too happy.
Oh. everyone in the whole
neighborhood is out there?
The whole neighborhood's
sitting out there?
Is Mrs. Swanson out there
with those stupid drop earrings?
Open the door. she's right here?
You know. maybe I
should put a dimmer on that.
Wouldn't that be a good idea?
So how'd you guys do
on that Christmas drive?
You were gone a long time. You
must have been working really hard.
We walked. like. 300 miles
around the whole neighborhood.
You're doing a good thing.
Why don't you go
wash up for dinner?
Tim!
Honey. can we just turn
down the Christmas lights
till after dinner's cooked?
Maybe that would
be a good idea. Yeah.
86. 87. 88. 89. 90.
$90.24.
Yeah. that's a major
amount of money.
We made 90 bucks.
If we made 90 bucks a
day and worked for 7 days.
we'd make. like. 200 bucks.
Brad. your math
tutor must be proud.
This is more money than we've
ever had on our bed before.
Yeah. if the money was ours.
we could buy 30
Rooster Man comic books.
Yeah. we could get
Barbarian 2 for Game Boy.
Yeah.
Too bad you don't get
paid collecting for charity.
If we were working
at our regular jobs.
we'd get paid salary.
How much do you think Dad makes?
I don't know. 3 bucks an hour.
Yeah.
And Al does most of the work.
I mean. we worked hard.
and I'm wearing out my shoes.
So?
So...
Charity. charity.
two for us.
I don't know. This is all
supposed to go to charity.
It will. I'm just taking a little
bit out for business expenses.
Besides. Mom always
says charity begins at home.
Oh. Tim. there you are.
Are you ready to shoot
our Christmas promo?
♪ Fa-la-la-la-la la-la-la-la ♪
You should try to cheer
up a little bit. Maureen.
Ho-ho-ho.
Well. look. it's a telephone
repairman from the North Pole.
And what would you like
for Christmas. little boy?
A new assistant.
Whoo! All righty.
it's your turn.
Here we go.
Ohh. Couldn't you
just eat him up?
Tim "The Elf Man" Taylor.
Oh. now don't be such a Grinch.
You looked adorable.
I've got a wonderful surprise.
You joined a convent
and took a vow of silence.
No. silly. I have booked some very special
musical guests for our Christmas show.
Guess who. Time's up.
Manhattan Transfer.
Manhattan Transfer? Didn't
you think about checking with me?
Tim. are you
forgetting? Producer.
Besides. who did
you want me to book -
those musical barking
dogs that sing "Jingle Bells"?
Yes! We've been trying
to get them for three years.
They won't do a cable show.
OK. now. come on.
Come on. think big-time
Christmas special.
Manhattan Transfer.
♪ Hmm-hmm-hmm...
♪ ...hmm ♪
All the Tool Time gang
sitting around the fireplace
all cuddly and cozy.
sipping cider with
cinnamon sticks.
Put a nail gun to my
temple and kill me right now.
OK. time to get
the promo rolling.
The sled is set.
Let's make magic.
Tim. Tim. Tim. come on.
Let's be good for
goodness' sake.
All right. all right.
but I'm driving.
Oh. now wait a minute. Tim. Tim.
Tim! You know. it's
against union rules
to let an elf drive a sleigh.
What? Besides. your legs -
What about 'em? Well.
they're just a little too short.
Al!
Ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
Just remember. it's not
over till it's over. fat boy.
Aw. now wait a minute. Tim.
Let's be professional
about this.
This is for charity.
It's for the children.
The least you can do
is wear your little elf hat.
Remember. Tim. to make
the snow machine work.
you just hit that button
on the back of the sled.
Yes. Maureen. I remember.
I'm the one that designed it.
Do you recall? Huh?
In 5. 4. 3. 2...
Look out for that mountain. Al.
Tim. Tim!
Ho!
Ho-ho-ho! Merry Christmas!
Join me - Santa -
and Tim "The..."
"The Elf Man" Taylor
for a very special
Christmas Tool Time.
We'll be kicking off our...
We'll be kicking off
our annual Tools for Tots drive
to raise money to build
playgrounds in the Detroit area.
Helping us out is our
very special guest.
The Manhattan Transfer.
So. until then. on
Donner. on Blitzen.
on Comet...
What's the matter. Santa?
You never flown
in a blizzard before?
Just...
Tim...
Tim?
Where are you two going?
I thought you were gonna help
me put these ornaments on the tree.
We're going back out collecting.
Wow. You guys are troupers.
You did this all day
yesterday and this morning.
Yeah. well. we only
made $5 this morning.
Well. that is $5 that the charity
didn't have before you started.
You're making a contribution.
You should be really
proud of yourselves.
Yeah. well. we are.
Thanks a lot. Mom.
All right. bye-bye!
Bye.
Honey. why'd you turn
the light off of Frosty?
There was a plane
headed for our house. Tim.
"Rooster Man. Rooster Man."
There's a whole stack of
these. It's a great comic.
"Barbarian 2 Game Boy." Did you
buy him this? I didn't buy him this.
No. but I wanted it.
Did you buy him those comics?
Unh-unh. but I bet Nana gave him
some Christmas money last weekend.
I don't believe it.
This is the coolest
watch in the world.
Time Commander chronograph.
What is that doing in Brad's backpack?
They love me. It's probably
my Christmas present.
How could they afford that? They're
saving their allowance or something.
This has three time
zones. its own built-in alarm.
It's good to 120
meters underwater.
You could be drowning and still
know exactly what time it is in Guam.
This is...
Ow! Ornaments! Ornaments!
Ornaments! Ornaments! Ornaments!
Whoa!
You... You sat...
You sat on a glass reindeer.
Pull it. Go!
You got an antler up your butt.
Pull it out of there!
Hey. OK. Just stop
bouncing around.
You're gonna get glass all over
the floor... Thanks for your concern.
Outside.
Ow. Ow. Ahh.
Come here. Pull this...
You got it out of
there? Well. I think so.
You'll find out
when you sit down.
Hi-ho-ho-ho. good neighbors.
Hi. Wilson. Oh. Merry
Christmas. Wilson.
Jill. I wanna thank you
for that very lovely
Smoky Farms gift box.
Oh. I'm so sorry.
I didn't realize that those little
cheese logs were actual size.
Well. don't be sorry.
They went perfectly
with the little bottle of rum
I got from the airlines.
And this is for you. good
neighbors. fresh from the oven.
Well. thank you. What is it?
That is a plum cake. Ooh.
On Christmas Eve. the people
of Hertfordshire. England.
take the cake. stick
it on a cow's horn.
then they throw
cider in her face.
The malls close
early over there.
No. no. no. Tim.
If the cow flicks
the cake forward.
it means it's going to
be a very good harvest.
Oh. Well. that's very
thoughtful of you. Wilson.
Well. Jill. it's all part of the
spirit of Christmas giving.
which you seem to have
instilled in Randy and Brad.
The look of joy
on their little faces
when I gave them that $10
contribution for charity this morning -
I was really quite moved.
Wait a minute. Did you say $10?
All the cash I had. Jill.
They wouldn't take a check.
Well. Feliz Navidad.
good neighbors.
♪ Off I go a-wassailing.
a-wassailing... ♪
Did you hear that?
I sure did. He can't
carry a tune at all.
No. he said that
he gave them $10.
Tim. they told me that they only
collected $5 the whole morning.
Ho-ho-ho.
The watch. the video
game. the comic books...
They're stealing
from the charity
or-or from your dresser
drawer or something.
I don't leave any money in
my dresser drawer. You take it.
Well. then they're
stealing from the charity.
I found this in Bugsy's drawer.
These were in
Baby Face's dresser.
Wait till I get my
hands on those...
And I found this in
Brad's little book bag.
A locket. Maybe your
Christmas present?
How nice. I can put
their little mug shots in it.
What are we gonna say to them?
I'll tell you what
I'm gonna say.
"The locket goes back.
Thanks for the watch."
Hi. We're home.
Well. well. well.
look who's home.
How did it go?
Oh. OK.
How much money you
think you brought in today?
Around $20.
So with the five that you
brought in this morning.
that would make 25?
Yeah. That's a lot. huh?
Yeah. plus the money
from the rest of the week.
Who wants to go first?
I will.
Well. uh. it was Randy's idea.
Thanks a lot.
Brad. Well. it was.
Cut it out. cut it out.
Sit down on the couch.
Both of you. sit down
and tell me where you come
up with a stupid idea like this.
Well. we were gonna get you
really neat Christmas presents.
Don't give me that. Yeah. I
can't live without Rooster Man.
The watch is for you. Dad.
And the locket's for Mom.
Well. no. that's for Jennifer.
You just don't get it. do you?
That money was supposed to go
to the Oak Lane
Children's Center.
You stole money out
of the hands of kids
who have next to
nothing for Christmas.
We weren't gonna take
all of it. just some of it.
Some of it or all of
it. it was still stealing.
We'll do extra chores
to work off the money.
You're darn right you'll do extra
chores to work off the money.
Then you're gonna take this
stuff back and get the money for it.
And then you're gonna go back to
the shelter. take them the money.
and you're gonna tell
them that you stole it.
But. Mom. they're
gonna think we're thieves.
Good. Brad.
I think you should just go up to your
room and think about what you did.
You can just stay up there
for the rest of the night.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Oh. it's gonna be
a lot of fun today.
We're gonna have a lot
of Tim Taylor holiday hits.
like putting up outdoor lighting to
get your whole neighborhood together.
Ho-ho-ho!
Don Ho? I don't think so.
St. Nick. And I wouldn't
be a bit surprised
if ol' St. Nick slid out of
this chimney a little later
to hand out gifts to
the studio audience.
Ho-ho-ho! Not yet. Not yet!
What I'd like to do first is
introduce our musical guests.
No. we couldn't get
the barking dogs.
Aw.
But we got a group
that sounds a lot like 'em.
Ha-ha-ha-ha. Just kidding.
I'd like to introduce The Manhattan
Transfer. ladies and gentlemen.
It's good to have you here.
I gotta admit I'm a big fan.
I've always wanted to know
who's Manhattan. who's Transfer?
Yeah. right. right.
No. that's the name of
the group. Tim. Come on.
We have our own names. Just
like the rest of us would have.
Well. I'm Janis.
I'm Cheryl. I'm Tim.
I'm Alan. but sometimes
people call me Al.
Tim and Al. Do you assist him?
I don't think so. Tim.
Ho-ho-ho!
Hey. Santa?
Shut up!
No. The Manhattan
Transfer will not be using
a backup band today
because they'll be
singing Acapulco.
Tim. actually.
it's "a cappella."
It's warm there. too. I
love it there. It's a nice spot.
Ladies and gentlemen.
The Manhattan Transfer.
1... 2.1. 2.
♪ You better watch
out. you better not cry
♪ You better not
pout. I'm tellin' you why
♪ Santa Claus is comin'
♪ To town
♪ He's makin' a
list. checkin' it twice
♪ Gonna find out
who's naughty or nice
♪ Santa Claus
is comi" to town...
Ho-ho-ho-oh! Tim!
Tim!
♪ He knows when you're awake
♪ He knows if you've
been bad or good
♪ So be good for goodness' sake
Tim! ♪ You better watch
out. you better not cry
♪ You better not pout.
I'm tellin' you why...
No. not my shoe.
Don't-Don't pull!
♪ ...to town
♪ To town ♪
Just keep going. keep going.
♪ All the boys... Tim.
where are you going?
♪ ...the snowman soon will play
♪ And they are sure
to get their wishes met
♪ When they hear
the words we say
♪ You better watch
out. you better not cry
♪ You better not
pout. I'm tellin' you why
♪ Santa Claus is comin'
♪ Santa Claus is comin' Tim?
♪ Santa Claus is comin' to town
♪ To town Tim.
♪ To town
Would you get me out of here?
Look out! Old Santa is back!
♪ Yeah... ♪
No. you don't need a chain saw.
Just pull me up. No! Tim!
Tim. don't cut through this!
Boy. I'm glad that's over.
Yeah. tell me about it.
Can you believe all those
kids down at the shelter?
Yeah. they didn't have anything.
and we're stealing
money from them.
And we have lots of stuff.
I guess we got it
pretty good. huh?
Come on. let's
clean up our room.
It was kind of weird the way
those kids were staring at us.
They were staring at you.
You just stood there
making monkey sounds.
Uhh! Uhh!
That was 'cause Mom
was poking me in the ribs.
She wanted you to say something.
I had to apologize
for the both of us.
So? I had to give
them the money.
You don't ever play
with this. do you. Randy?
No. not really.
Me neither.
We can give it to the shelter.
Hey. great idea.
We don't play with this. either.
and this is Mark's.
Dump it.
Randy. do you really think
Dad's gonna hang our
pictures up in the post office?
I hope you're kidding.
Oh. we can give 'em these.
OK. And there's a
lot of stuff in here.
Oh. there is? Yeah.
♪ It came upon...
♪ That glorious...
Poor Al. Al looks mad.
What was he saying?
He was...
He was saying. "Merry Christmas
and have a happy new year. Tim."
So did you. uh. did
you clean up your room?
Almost. but we wanted
to bring this down.
What?
We were just going
through some of our toys.
and we thought that maybe the kids
at the shelter could use some of them.
That's a really sweet idea.
Well. they're just some toys that
we don't play with that much anymore.
like this.
Or this.
Wait a minute. That's
Tournament Football.
I still play with
that thing. Dad.
All right. it's Christmas. but remember
- I'm still high score on that thing.
This is a really good idea. We'll
take you back to the shelter tomorrow.
OK. We have some
more stuff in the basement.
Just gather everything
up that you don't play with.
OK. Mark. jump in. Shut up.
I'm gonna get some toys.
OK.
♪ It came upon...
Gosh. they are so good.
Yeah. but they're
no barking dogs.
Tim. I thought you said you
were gonna return that watch.
I'm going to. but look. My
blood pressure. it's rising.
Honey. have you
seen the front yard?
Frosty's missing. I know.
Oh. it's not enough that Doc
Johnson wins the contest.
Now he's gotta
hijack my snowman?
Doc Johnson didn't take it.
I suppose a 17-foot plastic
snowman is hiding from me?
Does this look familiar?
Frosty?
He had a power surge
and suffered a meltdown.
Frosty is 17 feet
of pulsating light
generated by 120
volts of luminous flux
and 50.000 lumens per
second of uninterrupted power.
Ar-ar-ar-ar-ar.
This is low key?
I see spots.
Isn't this awesome?
Yeah. it would be perfect
if we had an airstrip
on the front lawn.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org